This is the truth behind the Li mansion hauntings.
The six of us worked together
just to punish
the killer of Elder Ding and his grandson.
That's a vicious lie!
That I hurt Elder Ding and his grandson...
Tell me this.
He was just a dirt poor old man.
Why would I bother hurting him?
You...
Jiang Huai,
tell us.
What was his motive for murder?
Go get the box.
The box is in the Li mansion's storeroom.
Madam!
Jiang Huai is just a storyteller.
Storytellers love making things up.
Shut up!
My dad was bought off by you,
but I wasn't.
Watch your mouth.
Don't make me smack you.
Benefactor Li,
Master Li.
You're obviously afraid of ghosts,
so why do you still live in this mansion?
Rumor has it
that the Li mansion has bad Feng Shui.
Every wife you marry dies.
But with so many good Feng Shui spots,
why did you seize Elder Ding's land
to build your mansion here?
I believe your real reason
lies in this jade pendant of yours.
Don't move!
What about the jade pendant?
Look closely, everyone.
The pattern on this jade pendant
is called the Flowing Cloud Pattern.
It's exclusive to Yuncang Kingdom royals.
Yuncang Kingdom,
because it was rich in gold,
was also known as the Kingdom of Gold.
Master.
Here, from the Li mansion's storeroom,
we found these Yuncang Kingdom artifacts.
Master said
these are all burial goods from a tomb.
Don't move!
What are you doing? Don't move!
Two years ago,
you appeared near Elder Ding's house.
He treated your injuries,
yet you plotted against his family.
All for
the Yuncang Kingdom's Golden Tomb, right?
Actually, you're not Benefactor Li at all.
You go by a much more notorious name.
You're Burrowing Rat.
One of the famous Four Bandits of Yanbei.
News of your tomb raiding
often appeared in the newspapers.
I've been keeping an eye on you all along.
The Four Bandits of Yanbei were infamous
and made front-page headlines every time.
However, two years ago,
they suddenly vanished without a trace,
and committed no more crimes.
Until I first saw Benefactor Li,
and noticed his enlarged knuckles
and darkened neck.
These are signs of years of hard labor.
But why would a wealthy master
do physical labor?
Later on,
Both in the storeroom and on him,
I found treasures of the Yuncang Kingdom.
The one who digs for the Four Bandits
is Burrowing Rat.
The time Benefactor Li made his fortune
perfectly matches their disappearance.
Burrowing Rat,
where are your three brothers?
Let me tell you,
500 years ago,
a Yuncang Kingdom prince named Qifeng...
Well, he
took his gold south to the Central Plains
to marry a princess.
But who knew that halfway there,
he would suddenly fall ill and die?
His followers
buried all this gold with him.
So,
this place right here...
is the Yuncang Kingdom's Golden Tomb!
I never imagined
that the Golden Tomb
would be deep in Lijia Town's forests,
and the Four Bandits of Yanbei found it!
Help me!
Elder Ding never imagined
that his act of kindness
would bring about his own demise.
Chunmei and her brothers are the killers.
The three sisters are their accomplices.
The six of them acted together.
This is the truth of the Li mansion case.
The so-called ghosts and spirits
are nothing but rumors.
Chunmei,
Dazhu,
Erzhu,
you resorted to vigilantism
instead of justice,
mistakenly killing the wives and Mengzhu.
You've committed intentional homicide.
The three sisters scared people as ghosts,
committing public intimidation.
To get revenge on Benefactor Li,
you killed so many innocent people.
How are your actions
any different from Benefactor Li's?
You are Unforgivable.
You must face the law.
Officers!
Take them back to the station.
Yes, sir.
Oh no.
It's almost seven.
I have to report to the provincial bureau.
I must beat my father to it.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Hello, Director Wu.
Good morning, Director Wu.
It's Mu Gui.
I'm asking you
to dismiss Lijia Town's Inspector,
Mu Ying, from her post.
Mu Gui.
You're the one being dismissed.
Director Wu.
I'm the one being dismissed?
There must be a mistake, Director Wu.
Director Wu?
Director Wu!
Chief!
From the Provincial Inspection Division.
They insisted on barging in.
I couldn't stop them.
You guys from the Inspection Division,
what are you doing in Lijia Town?
Mu Gui,
By order of Director Wu,
you are suspended and under investigation.
In Elder Ding's case, you're suspected of
accepting bribes,
dereliction of duty,
and letting criminals go free.
During your suspension and investigation,
your duties in Lijia Town are suspended.
Mu Ying will take over as Chief.
Mu Ying will get married to Benefactor Li.
She can't be Chief.
Besides,
out of the blue,
why is the provincial bureau suspending me?
The one who reported your misconduct
was none other than Mu Ying.
She asked me to inform you
the wedding is canceled.
Benefactor Li is a criminal suspect.
The Li mansion murder case
must still be investigated.
Take him away. Mu Ying reported me?
That's not right. That damn girl...
That's not right.
That's not right!
Let's go. Move it!
Mu Ying! Take him away!
That's not right!